Stop this!
No more! They're going to die!
What? Why?
This is exactly what they deserve.
You showed up late for a date with me, your own fiancée,
because you were too busy drinking the night away with these commoners.
Isn't that right?
How strange!
I didn't know a human could make a sound like that!
You learn something new every day!
Guess what? I knew this would happen.
I saw your future. I knew you'd be
getting wasted at the pub that morning.
You knew?!
Yes. The entire time, from the day I met you.
So, Leon.
Every man and woman here
got to spend the night with you, huh?
I'm getting jealous.
Please, stop!
The fault is all my own!
They've done nothing to deserve this!
Nothing?
Nothing at all!
Really?
Well then, here's a question for you, my beloved Leon.
Did you willingly choose to spend
all night with these filthy Anemonians
instead of spending the morning with me?
Because if so, these people are innocent,
and I shall release them.
Yes, I take responsibility for all of it! So please!
However...
That means you committed treason against me,
and by extension the Kingdom of Freesia, right?
That's grounds for Freesia to launch
an immediate invasion of the Kingdom of Anemone.
Invasion?
What else would you expect?
After all, you've humiliated me, the queen.
We're going to raze
your whole nation to the very ground.
If they are the ones to blame, then they will be executed here.
If you are to blame, then we go to war.
Well, which is it?
Are they at fault?
Or... Are you?
I am...
not to blame!
He's lying!
That's what I thought!
Prince Leon!
That's the only explanation!
He's wrong! Please, no!
We're innocent!
So, Leon.
Do you love me?
Y-Yes, I love you! I love you!
I-I-I lo... I love you.
S-S-So I beg you...
Prove it to me, then.
Execute them all, by your own hand.
Prince Leon...
I had faith in you...
Hurry...
We beg you...
Just kill me...
Did you hear that?
Everyone's suffering!
Hurry and put them out of their misery.
Come on, do it now, sweet prince!
I love you so much, Leon.
Why...
Why am I here?
Every day's unique, you get one chance at it
So you'd better make it count
When people flaunt morality
You've gotta beware they've got their own agenda
Somewhere in your head, there's a voice that's messin' with ya
Don't ever let it turn you 'round
It can't even blow all that hot air it's full of
Get yourself in gear and live however you wanna
Live so fast that the claws of despair will languish in your dust
And you'll be the one with an agenda that they'll all see as just
Keep on shouldering the world around you
Keep on doubting every thought that's bound you
If things go awry, keep pushing through
And know that everything'll work in the end
If you find it's in your power to change the world
I'm sure you can make the future bright
We'll blaze on ahead until we track down the route we want to take
We'll keep trying every door until we find one that goes our way
The Cruel Queen
and the Truth
Say, mister, did you get left behind?
I wonder what kind of fun he got up to
before he made it here.
Leave him be!
Seems like the blokes he was with
just got dragged along on his little bender.
Whatever, let the guy have as much fun as he wants!
They left plenty of coin behind, after all!
We're drinkin' 'til the sun comes up!
My people.
I'm so close to their voices,
and their smiles, like I wanted to be.
That's right...
I wanted to see them.
You must not leave the castle.
What?
Who told me that?
Especially on the last day.
The last day?
What... did that mean?
That is when you will lose everything.
I have a feeling it was very important.
Looks like he's struggling.
I feel a little better.
You'll be forced to drink excessively, and at the pub the morning after...
Pub?
Am I drunk, then?
Alcohol's never made me feel like this before.
...you will lose the trust
of your people, as well as the king.
Lose their trust?
I-I don't want that.
Hey, I sure would like to see his face.
Me too. Let's get this hat off of him.
No!
I can't let them see my face!
No! No, no, no, no!
Someone... Help me!
Huh? What?!
I can't see a thing!
What's going on?
Who put out the lights?!
Something's covering the lamps and I can't get them lit again!
Who the hell covered them up?!
Up you go.
That was some pretty good booze.
Thanks for the drinks.
Hey there, Mistress.
Running a little late, eh?
Val.
Thank you for all you've done this past week.
Got your goods right over here.
Quite the pretty boy, isn't he?
You've already moved him to safety?
Yeah.
Just like you asked.
I want you to watch over Crown Prince Leon.
He got smashed at the pub,
and they almost took his hat off...
but right before then, I knocked out the lights,
snatched him up, and came here.
It was super awesome!
Val.
He was awake when I grabbed him...
But after I carried him
all the way here, he fell back asleep.
Philip.
Val, you'll all need to join us.
Please tell me more about what happened.
Okay.
Sure.
Lady Jeanne!
How is my fiancé faring?
Well...
Something seems to be wrong with him.
I suspect that he's—
Eh? Making him drink water isn't going to help.
The drug's already running through his system.
What do you mean by "drug"?
Isn't that obvious?
Alcohol alone would never leave him like that.
Yes, I agree.
Sure, they forced him to drink some booze at the pub,
but this is clearly the work of a drug.
It's a concoction of sleeping pills and narcotics.
It rarely gets used because of the high price tag,
but in my experience it's especially useful for human trafficking
when you need to nab a target.
Don't set a bad example for Khemet!
Ow!
It's a powerful drug.
How could this happen to a crown prince?
You're making a mountain out of a molehill, Sir Knight.
The effects of the drug will wear off
if we let him sleep for the night.
But this is no small incident!
Someone at the pub must've drugged him!
Not quite. The drug was already
in the boy when he got there.
I'd been keeping tabs on him at the castle, but...
A couple of men literally carried him out of there.
Couldn't even walk on his own.
I followed them, and not only did they bring him to the pub,
but they forced alcohol on him
before throwing down some money and leaving.
He was probably drugged first
and then dragged out there.
I mean, I got to enjoy some good booze
thanks to them, though.
So he was given the drug while still at the castle?!
Isn't that a catastrophic security breach?!
If that's true, then it's more than just a breach.
This was an abduction.
Drugging a prince to take him
out of the castle is beyond a serious crime.
Elder Sister?
Ooh, such anger from my mistress!
The people who set Prince Leon up...
are second prince Erwin and third prince Homer.
In the game, they frequently came to visit
their heartbroken brother Leon.
Then, if Tiara takes the Leon route,
she happens to meet them outside of Leon's room,
and she learns some of the truth
of what happened two years earlier.
They were jealous of their
older brother's claim to the throne
and spread bad rumors about him.
All the talk of him being flirtatious
and womanizing were just baseless lies!
In the game, when Tiara probes further...
We only gave him a little wine,
then had some servants take him down to the pub.
A little wine? Yeah, right!
The brothers said Leon got drunk from some celebratory wine and they tended to him
before leaving him in his room.
Then they claimed that Leon drunkenly wandered out of the castle by himself,
which Leon himself took as fact!
At least until Tiara uncovers the truth
and tells him what his brothers really did.
They set up their own brother by drugging him!
Those pieces of trash!
I thought it would be okay if I just convinced Leon not to leave the castle.
But it turned out that wasn't even the problem!
And worse yet, from what I know about those brothers...
They will not get away with this.
When Prince Leon awakens tomorrow,
I will explain the situation to him.
As fellow royalty, I cannot let this absurdity stand!
I will put a stop to them in this world!
Where am I?
Are you awake, then?
Who are you?
My name is Callum.
Do you remember what happened last night?
Last night...
I had wine with my brothers...
Listen calmly, Your Highness.
We found you collapsed at a pub last night
and took you to safety.
At a pub?
Oh no! I'm late!
What time is it?! I have to go!
Please take it easy.
All is well.
We will see you to the castle.
I'm deeply grateful for your help.
And my apologies, but I must get home immediately.
I have to go see my fiancée!
There's no need for that, Prince Leon.
Pride?
Why are you here?
I was concerned after I gave you advice that night,
so I came here undercover to see you.
Please excuse my doing so.
Prince Stale is here as well?!
You mustn't, Prince Leon!
A member of a royal family should never beg pardon from a false charge like this!
Pride!
I'm sorry.
Even though you went out of your way
to warn me that night, I still...
It's okay.
I know everything that happened.
I know you were drugged,
and that you were made to leave the castle against your will.
I also know the rumors about your womanizing
around town are entirely groundless.
Prince Leon.
The ones who drugged you and tried to frame you
are your own brothers.
It can't be!
You remember nothing after drinking that wine last night, correct?
If so, then let's head to the castle,
and talk everything over with His Majesty the King.
We can't.
If we do, we'll lose the heirs to the throne...
Those two must've done it for the good of the country!
If they were thinking about the country,
they would never have done such a wicked thing!
Enough already! Wake up, Leon Adonis Coronaria!
Where does your purpose lie?!
Remember what you stand for! Your heartfelt desire!
Right now, you have me on your side.
You have my brother and our knights, too!
I'm sure if we go to him now,
the king will listen to what you say!
Prince Leon...
What is it that you love above all else?
I don't know.
I love you, Pride Royal Ivy...
and you alone.
Give it up, Leon!
That was not from your heart!
I am not the one you love!
Embrace your own desires!
This is your only chance!
Before everything slips through your fingers!
Face your true feelings!
Prince Leon, what you will always love
from the bottom of your heart...
are the people of your nation!
But I can't!
I have to leave this country!
Otherwise, these impure needs I have
will affect the citizens I love...
I've fallen in love with my people...
But I cannot expose them to my desires,
my narcissism, my possessiveness!
I can't become king!
What makes you think you're unfit for the throne?
There is nothing impure about your desire.
Whose approval are you searching for?
The people's, right?
Wanting the people to approve of you,
or wanting to become a king the people desire...
Where is the sin in any of that?
When did you become a narcissist?
You've always loved the people, never yourself.
You opened your heart to them.
Or are you telling me that interacting
with the people has given you a big head?
What do you mean by "possessiveness"?
Are you talking about your desire to be loved by your citizens?
That's only natural!
Because you cherish the people of this country!
And have for a long, long time!
That isn't possessiveness.
It's precisely because you've dedicated yourself
time and time again to the happiness of your people
that you hoped to be loved.
Besides, even if the people didn't love you,
you would still be a champion for them.
Because you are a respectable person
who always puts others ahead of himself!
In the game world,
Leon remained in the Kingdom of Freesia as Pride's fiancé.
As the days went on and she continued tormenting him, he still endured it all.
And that wasn't because he had no other place to go.
He did it to maintain the alliance between Freesia and his beloved country.
Even heartbroken and trapped in a room
he could never escape from, he held fast.
You mean, these feelings are okay?
They're not impure?
That's right.
It's okay for you to embrace your desires.
Because your noble heart will surely guide you down the correct path.
I don't want to leave the Anemone Kingdom!
Trade relations are going well!
In the future, we'll gather a lot of resources
and this nation will undoubtedly become rich!
Children in the city told me
that in the future, they want to collect goods from around the world and become merchants!
A month ago, a farm family on the outskirts smiled
and told me that they had cultivated new produce!
They said they wanted me to try it someday!
The last time I went to town,
a woman let me hold her baby!
She'd even named him after me!
She hoped her child would
grow up to be as kind as I am!
Even after my bad reputation spread around town,
everyone, every last one of them
said they believed in me!
They smiled at me, without fail!
I love it!
I love this country!
There you have it.
That is your truth.
Prince Leon.
This is why I'm here.
I came all this way to help you get everything back.
All of it?
We'll go together.
All of us will join you.
If you embrace your resolve and take my hand...
I will do everything in my power
to ensure your happiness!
The Most Heretical Last Boss Queen:
From Villainess to Savior.
Episode 4: "The Cruel Queen Makes a Declaration".
The Cruel Queen Makes a Declaration